So people will send me videos of people talking about me on the internet saying, I used to follow
Amanda Seals, especially during Black Lives Matter, and she switched up. I never switched up.
Black Lives Matter is literally about how this country, as the oppressor, does not prioritize
the protection of Black lives the way that it does white lives. So why do you think I would be okay
with Palestinian lives not being prioritized when they are the ones being taken in droves,
when they are the ones who have been put asunder an apartheid regime for 75 years? I didn't switch
up. You did. And if you have left the company of my thoughtful bosom, if you now find yourself in
the company of MAGA, of racists, of people who are clearly not intellectual, ask yourself, how did I
get here? Baby, you took the propaganda to express the colonist's bill, and now you're hanging with
your people, oppressors.